[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The science called myrmecology deals with the study of which of the following?", "correct_answer": "Ants", "incorrect_answers": ["Wasps", "Centipedes", "Insects"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Is the Moa related to the kiwi, a living species of flightless bird from New Zealand?", "correct_answer": "No", "incorrect_answers": ["Yes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "According to the Medieval Bestiary hyenas have the ability to change their sex.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was the first U.S. President born in the USA?", "correct_answer": "Van Buren", "incorrect_answers": ["Madison", "John Adams", "Washington"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If the world were a village of 1000 people, what would the life expectancy of the villagers be?", "correct_answer": "66", "incorrect_answers": ["76", "82", "71"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the first name of the character Masterson in the musical comedy Guys and Dolls?", "correct_answer": "Sky", "incorrect_answers": ["Uri", "Dom", "Job"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the English name for the first book of the Bible?", "correct_answer": "Genesis", "incorrect_answers": ["Exodus", "Mathew", "Luke"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What animal part is used for the preparation of the traditional South African dish called Mala Mogodu?", "correct_answer": "Tripe", "incorrect_answers": ["Liver", "Tongue", "Kidney"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In chemistry, if you mix an acid with a base you would get these chemicals.", "correct_answer": "Water and a salt", "incorrect_answers": ["Water and carbon dioxide", "Carbon dioxide and water", "A salt and oxygen"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In this country one out of ten people owns a bicycle.", "correct_answer": "Denmark", "incorrect_answers": ["Belgium", "Sweden", "France"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This TV series, which aired in 1982-1983, starred Sarah Jessica Parker, Jami Gertz, Tracy Nelson, and Amy Linker.", "correct_answer": "Square Pegs", "incorrect_answers": ["Mr. Novak", "Room 222", "Welcome Back, Kotter"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who plays Chris Adams in Guns of the Magnificent Seven, the second sequel to The Magnificent Seven?", "correct_answer": "George Kennedy", "incorrect_answers": ["James Coburn", "Yul Brynner", "Steve McQueen"]}]